netcracker.com 2012-06-25

# NetCracker. Privacy Statement

NetCracker Technology Corporation (“NetCracker”) respects your privacy. This Privacy Statement informs you of our privacy practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected online and how that information is used. This statement is readily available on our home page and at the bottom of every NetCracker web page. 

**The following aspects of NetCracker’s policy are discussed below:**

#### 1\. Sites covered by this Privacy Statement

#### 2\. Links to non-NetCracker websites 

#### 3\. Collection of personal information

#### 4\. How we use your information

#### 5\. How we share your information

#### 6\. Children’s privacy

#### 7\. NetCracker general communications

#### 8\. Changes to this statement

#### 9\. Contacting us

How NetCracker uses the following automatic data collection tools is also discussed: 

  * Cookies
  * Web beacons
  * Embedded web links
  * NetCracker ads on third-party websites 
  * Information-gathering tools 

#### 1\. Sites Covered by This Privacy Statement

NetCracker is a global organization, with legal entities, business processes, management structures, and technical systems that cross borders. This Privacy Statement applies only to this NetCracker-owned website and domain.

#### 2\. Links to Non-NetCracker Websites

The NetCracker website may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. If you access those links, you will leave the NetCracker website. NetCracker does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from NetCracker's practices. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites. The personal data you choose to provide to or that is collected by these third parties is not covered by the NetCracker Privacy Statement. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your personal information.

#### 3\. Collection of Personal Information 

NetCracker may collect and use personal information to understand your needs and interests and to serve you better. 

NetCracker may collect information during your visit to a NetCracker website through our automatic data collection tools, which include web beacons, cookies, embedded web links, and other commonly used information-gathering tools. These tools collect certain standard information that your browser sends to our website, such as your browser type and language, access times, and the address of the website from which you arrived at a NetCracker website. They may also collect information about your Internet Protocol (IP) address, clickstream behavior (i.e., the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with the NetCracker website), and product information. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers use IP addresses to communicate on the Internet, allowing users to browse and shop. NetCracker also uses some of these automatic data collection tools in connection with certain emails sent from NetCracker and therefore may collect information using these tools when you open the email or click on a link contained in the email. 

#### 4\. How We Use Your Information

If NetCracker were to collect your information, it would be to understand your needs and interests to help NetCracker deliver a consistent and personalized experience. For example, NetCracker may use your information to: 

  * Communicate with you about products and services
  * Update you on new services and benefits

#### 5\. How We Share Your Information

NetCracker will not sell, rent, or lease your personal information to others. NetCracker may share information with companies working on our behalf and NetCracker-owned business entities. 

Circumstances may arise where, whether for strategic or other business reasons, NetCracker decides to sell, buy, merge, or otherwise reorganize businesses in some countries. Such a transaction may involve the disclosure of personal information to prospective or actual purchasers, or the receipt of it from sellers. It is NetCracker’s practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions. 

#### 6\. Children's Privacy

NetCracker does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and does not target its websites to children under 13. We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. 

#### 7\. NetCracker General Communications 

NetCracker general communications provide information about products, services, and/or support. 

#### 8\. Changes to This Statement

NetCracker will undertake reasonable efforts to notify you of material changes to this statement. 

#### 9\. Contacting Us

We value your opinions. If you have comments or questions about our Privacy Statement, please send them to [Webmaster@NetCracker.com](mailto:Webmaster@NetCracker.com).

© 2009 NetCracker Technology Corp. All rights reserved.
